<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>A Mere Reed</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2022-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>Yet another "outsider lands a coding job" success story</title><link href="/yet-another-outsider-lands-a-coding-job-success-story.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Jeff Nicholas</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-08-20:/yet-another-outsider-lands-a-coding-job-success-story.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;There is a seemingly infinite number of cases of non-tech people getting in to the tech industry, more than enough for other outsiders to feel good about their odds of making the same career change. I've seen it happen with a few musician friends/acquaintances, and read countless blogs and …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There is a seemingly infinite number of cases of non-tech people getting in to the tech industry, more than enough for other outsiders to feel good about their odds of making the same career change. I've seen it happen with a few musician friends/acquaintances, and read countless blogs and reddit posts about people describing how they got coding jobs without a "real" coding background. This is my entry into that storied tradition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started my first professional coding job (x) weeks ago. I don't have an academic background in programming, and I never attended a bootcamp or took a single programming class. Everything I learned came from online tutorials and Google/Stack Overflow. I actually had to stop myself from writing this article as soon as I got the job because, for every story about someone like me getting such a job, there is another story of that same person feeling out of their depth in their new field. Was I going to end up in the same boat? Would I get exposed as some kind of fraud and get let go within two months?&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="posts"></category></entry></feed>